Guide to the Edwin "Bud" Shrake Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Correspondence, 1936-2009, undated
  - Alphabetical, 1954-2009, undated
    - Roussel, Elvera, 1978-1987, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Rudman, Michael, 1969-1996 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Rudman, Michael, 2000-2003 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Rudman, Michael, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Rudman, Michael, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Rudman, Michael, 2008-2009 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Sanders, Ed, 1969-1978, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Schwartz, Marvin, 1972-1997, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Shrake, Ben (and Dawna Locker), circa 1965-2009 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Shrake, Caleb and Heather, 1990-2006, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Shrake, Creagan/Alan and Eunai, circa 1965-2006 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Shrake/Strait, Joyce and Emert, Victor, 1961-2000, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Shrake, Ruth and Ed / Bruce and Donna, 1962-1983, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Simmons, David, 1964-1972, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Stagg, Carolyn Willyoung (Lester Lewis Associates), 1957-1967, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Wiatt, Jim (ICM), 1978-1997, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Chronological, 1936-2009, undated
    - December 24, 1936 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - circa 1960-1969 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - 1958-1963 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - 1964 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - 1965 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - 1969-1975 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - 1976 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - 1977 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - circa 1970-1979 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - 1980 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - January - June 1981 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - July - December 1981 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - January - June 1982 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - July - December 1982 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - 1983 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - January - June 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - July - December 1984 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - 1985 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - 1986 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - January - June 1987 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - July - December 1987 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - 1988 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - 1991 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - 1992 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - 1993 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - possible 1993 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - 1994 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - possible 1994 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 1995 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - possible 1995 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - January - June 1996 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - July - December 1996 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - possible 1996 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - 1997 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - possible 1997 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - circa 1990-1999 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - 2002-2005 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Restricted until April 25, 2029 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Financial Papers, 1963-2000
  This series is arranged chronologically, and contains receipts, income taxes, expense reports, financial statements and other documents related to various aspects of Shrake's life. The financial records tend to give snapshots of Shrake's financial situation and lifestyle through the years, rather than a complete picture. Besides expense reports from Sports Illustrated that go to 1976, the financial records do not contain any documents between 1972 and 1980.
  - Bank Statement, January 24, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Time Inc. Expense Reports, 1964-1976 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Income Taxes, 1965-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Travel Receipts, circa 1966-1969 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Bank Account Ledgers with receipts and notes, circa 1967-1972 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Author Purchases (Doubleday), 1968 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Reimbursement Letters, 1980-1985 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Buttercup Property, 1981 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Computer Price Quotes, circa 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, 1982-1998 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Lost Creek Country Club, circa 1980-1989 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Air Travel, circa 1980-1999 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - WGA West Pension Plan dispute, 1988-1990 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - WGA West Pension Plan dispute, 1991-1992 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Notes, 1994, undated (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - WGA, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Car, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Notice of Appraised Value, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Callaway Golf expenses, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Time Warner Employee's Pension Plan, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Fortis Health Insurance, 1997-1998 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Tax Appraisal, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - West Ave. Joint Venue, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Corporations, 1969-1995, undated
  This seriesdocuments the two corporations that Shrake started and operated: Mad Dog, Inc. and East Pole Corporation. The Mad Dog, Inc. Corporate Structure and correspondence reflect the company's satirical nature. The East Pole Corporation materials include receipts, reports, a budget, tax records, pension plan and an embosser.
  - Mad Dog, Inc., 1969-1972, undated
    - Incorporation Documents, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records, 1969-1970 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Notes, correspondence, 1970-1972, undated (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Structure, undated (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - East Pole Corp., 1977-1996
    - Reports and budget, 1977-1979 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, circa 1979-1990 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and IRS, 1989-1996, undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Defined Benefit Pension Plan, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Embosser (Box 150)
- Legal Papers, 1977-1997, undated
  Seven subjects of a legal nature are documented in this series: Austin Sun Publishing Company, Jan Demetri, ICM Contracts, Gary DeShazo, D.W.I., Buttercup Mountain and Manny Newburger. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - Austin Sun Publishing Company, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Jan Demetri, 1977-1995 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - ICM Contracts, 1981-1991 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Gary DeShazo, 1981-1993, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Gary DeShazo, 1994-1995 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Gary DeShazo, 1996-1997 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - D.W.I., 1982-1983 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Buttercup Mountain, 1989-1991 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Manny Newburger, 1990, undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Research, circa 1954-2006
  Shrake kept subject files on a wide variety of topics, often having to do with ideas for writing projects. These files make up the Subject Files sub-series and are the bulk of the Research series.They are arranged alphabetically by subject. Also included in the Research series are the Notes and Notebooks sub-series, and books and general research. The series is arranged chronologically by sub-series
  - Subject Files, 1954-2006, undated
    - The American, circa 1972 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Bad Bob Buck: Notes, circa 1975-1985 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Bad Bob Buck: Clippings, circa 1975-1985 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Banquet, circa 1977 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Baseball novel, circa 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Bigfoot Wallace, circa 1983-1985 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Bonnie and Clyde, circa 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Books on order, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Brute Demon / Lights Out, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Characters, circa 1981 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Dallas Women, 1988-1989 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Despoblado, circa 1978 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Dirty Dealing, circa 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Drug information, 1983-1984 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - The Dublin Project, 1998-1999 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - E. Snow Jr., circa 1981 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Films, circa 1973-1978 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Futures (recruiting movie), circa 1983 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Futures 1: No folder, circa 1960-1980 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Futures 1: Miscellaneous, circa 1954-1964 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Futures 1: Blue Baboons, undated (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Futures 1: Duane Wrote That Song, circa 1981 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Futures 1: Archie, circa 1981 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Futures 1: Rodney, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Futures 1: Golf Movie, undated (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Futures 2, undated (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Gambling, circa 1971-1973 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - God, 1983-1988 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Hydroponics, 1975, undated (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - The Hunts, circa 1974-1980 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Information, circa 1970-1981 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - L. King Forward, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Milch, David, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Music, circa 1975-1985 (Box 128, Folder 3-4)
    - The Mystery of the Atom, circa 1999 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Oil Business, 1962, undated (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Polo, circa 1977 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Projects, 1994-1995 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Raining Hard, circa 1974 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Religion in Sports, circa 1970-1974 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Sports Illustrated box: clippings, circa 1964-1970 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Table Dancing / Eddy Donna, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Tantrums, circa 1973-1977 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Texas Rangers, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Texas Revolution game, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Things To Be Used, 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - U.S. – Mexican War, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Utica Blue Sox, 1983-1984 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Writing, circa 1974-1984 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Notes and Notebooks, 1969-1995, undated
    - Sports Illustrated assignments, 1969-1975 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - General, circa 1965-1995 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - General, undated (Box 130, Folder 4-5)
  - Books, 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - General research, circa 1954-2003 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Personal Papers, 1900-2009, undated
  This series contains materials belonging to Shrake of a more personal nature and is arranged chronologically. The oldest item in this series, and in the collection, is Shrake's father's baby dress. Also included are certificates, clippings about Shrake and friends, photographs of Shrake, family and friends, scrapbooks, short stories written for class, two typewriters, a briefcase Shrake used for traveling on Sports Illustrated assignments, Shrake's leather office chair, artwork by Shrake and friends, property maintenance records, drafts of speeches, among other materials.
  - Separation sheet for Father's baby dress – item is in box 150 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Father's baby dress, 1900 (Box 150)
  - Certificates, 1931-1960 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1936-2008, undated
    - General, 1936-2008, undated (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Mention of Shrake or friends, 1960-2004, undated (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Articles about Shrake, 1962-2008 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Articles about friends, 1970-2005, undated (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - About Shrake from Linda Vance, circa 1983-1988 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Texas Walk of Stars Induction, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Ann Richards, 1988-2006, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Ann Richards obituaries, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, circa 1940-2004
    - Family, circa 1940-1967 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Shrake and friends, circa 1953-2000 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Slides, circa 1966 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Dick Growald, circa 1966-1980 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - General, circa 1970-2004 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Ann Richards and Shrake, circa 1990-1999 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbooks, circa 1944-1951 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Short stories for English classes, circa 1950 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Skyriter portable typewriter, 1953 (Box 147)
  - Contents of wallet, circa 1956-1961 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - General, 1962-1998, undated (Box 134, Folder 5-6)
  - General, circa 1983 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Artwork, 1952-2000, undated
    - Madigliani art book, 1952 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Son's drawings, circa 1960-1969 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Shiva's Headband, circa 1960-1969 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Richard Growald's drawings, circa 1960-1969 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Jack Jaxon's notebook, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Jim Franklin's calendar and drawing, 1975, undated (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Blackie Sherrod's paintings, circa 1990 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Shrake's paintings and drawings, 2000, undated (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Unknown, undated (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Travel-related materials, circa 1960-1969 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - The New Wedding book, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Smith-Corona typewriter (Box 148)
  - "EAS" briefcase (Box 149)
  - Brown leather chair, circa 1970-1979 (Map-case Upper A - Aisle 2)
  - Home - House maintenance, circa 1980-1986 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Home - Yard, circa 1982 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Home - Wish List, circa 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Home - Pets, circa 1980-1989 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Speeches and remarks, 1981-2006, undated (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Writers Guild, circa 1981-1985 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Business ventures - Pasta Canata, 1983-1985 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Business ventures - Cowboy TV Network/Outlaw Music Channel, 1989-1991 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Golf - Information, equipment, circa 1982 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Golf - Tournaments, 1995-1996, undated (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Resume, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Awards, honors, and events, 1987-2009 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Medical, 1992, 2007 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Associations, 1998-2007 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Calendars, 2003-2004 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Genealogy, undated (Box 136, Folder 9)
- Other Writers, 1968-2007, undated
  Shrake kept files of works by various writers, which are kept in this series. Some of these files contain editing notes by Shrake or correspondence from the writer. The series is arranged alphabetically by author's last name. Included are the production files for Another Pair of Aces, a TV movie written by Rob Gilmer that was a sequel to Shrake and Cartwright's Pair of Aces. Shrake was a co-producer of this movie. In the late 1990s, Roger Young wrote a screenplay for Blessed McGill, and worked with Shrake and G.W.Bailey to get it produced. The drafts and correspondence from this failed effort are included here. Shrake's good friends Gary Cartwright, Dan Jenkins, Larry L. King, Jay Milner, Willie Morris and Bill Wittliff have works in this series as well — often more than one.
  - Arthur, Robert Alan – "Indians", 1974 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Brammer, Shelby – "Pass with Care" and "Sitcom", 1981-1986 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Brammer, Sidney – "Kicking the Habit", undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Stan – "The Loneliness of a Long-Distance Producer", 1991 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Broyles, Bill – "The Girl from Moscow", 2006 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Cartwright, Gary - "Dirty Dealing in the Lonestar State", 1976-1978 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Cartwright, Gary - "Doing Time", undated (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Cartwright, Gary - "This is a Recording", 1968 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Cherry, Don – "Don Cherry's Jubilee", undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Crumley, James – "Save the Last Dance for the Bear", 1982 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Egan, Tom – "Limo", 1979 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Friedkin, Fine, Shaw – "Blessed McGill", 1981 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" - Correspondence, clippings, 1990-1991, undated (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" - First Draft (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" - Shooting Script, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" - Shooting Script, 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" - Production (Box 138, Folder 3-5)
  - Gilmer, Rob – "Another Pair of Aces" -Shooting Schedule (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Growald, Richard – "We Americans" column, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Hawk, Dave – "100 Years of Bass", circa 1978 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Hoggard, James –"Elevator Man: The Bobby Johnson Story", undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Howard, Klane, Axelrod – "Every Little Crook and Nanny", 1971 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Jenkins, Dan - Columns, 1986-1988, undated (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Jenkins, Dan - "Dead Solid Perfect", 1974 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Jenkins, Dan - "Don't Write Me Nothin' That Rhymes", 1987 (Box 140, Folder 7-9)
  - Jenkins, Dan - "Greatamerica", 1981 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Jenkins, Dan - "Texas Rag", 1981 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Jenkins, Dan - "What's Cooking?", undated (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Karp and Willis – "Smoke", 1980 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Katkov, Norman – "Grand Jury", 1969 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - King, Larry L. - Magazine articles, 1994, undated (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - King, Larry L. - "Breaking Balls", 1996 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - King, Larry L. - "The Dead Presidents' Club", 1996 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - King, Larry L. - "Texas Then and Now...", 1985 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - King, Larry L. - "Willie Morris: A Man of Many Parts", 2001 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Kunik, Anika – "Kissed by Noon", undated (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Margolin and Parker – "The Wileys", 1969 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Marquiss, Twister – "Bud Shrake: One Writer's Reader's Response to a Writer's Writer", 2008 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Martin, Jeanette – "The Last Cowboy", circa 1991 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - McGrath and Sweeney – "Loose Women", 1982 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Tim – one-man Ambrose Bierce play, undated (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Milner, Jay - book reviews, 1970-1998 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Milner, Jay - "Red Headed Stranger", 1977, undated (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Morris, Willie – "New York Days", 1991 (Box 142, Folder 8-9, Box 143, Folder 1-2)
  - Nelson, Susie – "Heart-worn Memories", undated (Box 143, Folder 3-5)
  - Pacheco, Ferdie – "The Great T and A Travelling Circus...", undated (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Petrie Jr., Daniel – "Beverly Hills Cop", 1984 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Pipkin, Turk –"Everyone's Meeting at RIP's", 1990 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Reynolds, Jonathan – "Geniuses", 1981 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Roussel, Elvera – "The Old Place", 1979 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Rudman, Michael – "Birdie", 1988 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Shafter, M.D. – "The Past", undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Sharp, Alan –"Blessed McGill", undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Sharp, Alan and Oliver Stone – "Pancho Villa and Tom Mix", December 1, 1986, undated (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Sheehy, Sandy – "Flesh and Blood", 1980 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Shelton, Gilbert – "Feds 'n' Heads", 1968 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Sherrod, Blackie – "Get Him to the Church", undated (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Shrake, Ben – "Space Missionary", undated (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Slusher, Katherine (a.k.a. "Candy Barr") – poetry, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Sturges, Preston – "Down Went McGinty", undated (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - unknown author – "Ball Chopping", undated (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - unknown author – "It's Always Yesterday Again", undated (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - unknown author – "Sweet Willie", undated (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - unknown author – untitled fiction typescript photocopy, undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - various authors – "GOAT: A Tribute to Muhammad Ali", 2001 (Box 152)
  - West, Tar – "The Iron Tourniquet", 1972 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Wheatley, Randall – "Fish Camp", August 1985 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Wheatley, Randall – "Fish Camp", October 1985 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Wheatley, Randall – "Fish Camp", March 1986 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Wittliff, Bill - "Barbarossa", undated (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Wittliff, Bill - "The Endurance", 1999 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Wittliff, Bill - "The Flying Tiger", 2007 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Wittliff, Bill - "Whirligig", undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - draft, correspondence, notes, 1998-1999 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - correspondence and draft, April 22, 1998 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - draft, September 1998 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - notes and draft, November 1998 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - correspondence and draft, March 3, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Young, Roger – "Blessed McGill" - draft, September 5, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 8)